If there is that one...
Charge
It's not a charge.
If you're re-elected...
I mean, re-election.
on the internet
Change.
I see. So, everyone is throwing in their money.
So it's started?
It's going on and on and on.
We've already started, and you're still throwing money at us.
May I?
I'm sorry.
Oh...
It looks like it's starting.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Yes, I mean...
Yes?
What's it like?
How are you feeling, you ask?
How do you feel now?
That's a dangerous question.
Let's not do that.
I don't know what's going to come out.
That's why we're going to be live again this week.
Thank you very much.
So...
Well then...
Let's start with a bang!
Let's get started right away.
I look forward to working with you today.
Who is it?
I don't know.
That's why I'm here.
Well, well, well...
What do you think of Christmas?
Just a group of friends?
Yes.
Do you get together and do things? I'm working.
But that's the way it is.
Why do you have lessons and deliveries on Christmas Day...
It seems like you had to include it today.
Can we talk about that with the office?
This is a live broadcast, so please, let's talk about that.
But that's the way it is in the entertainment business.
So we're having a lovely Christmas with the members.
We sometimes exchange gifts with other members.
Oh, I want to, but they don't bring gifts.
After all, some of us have been doing this for about 10 years now.
Here comes the Christmas man!
Fear Christmas man
I'm afraid of the Christmas man.
I'm sorry, but I get a little excited in December.
He said he'd get me a present.
No, no, no.
Not a wow.
Tell my favorite that I don't like this kind of guy.
Who doesn't like this guy?
I don't like that.
I'd say that, but I kind of admire it.
I don't say it, but I admire a guy who can say it like that.
There certainly aren't.
I'm sure there are guys like that.
Have you ever said that?
Is there anyone who has?
You'd probably be turned off.
But now...
But what if it's between the two of you? Like boyfriend and girlfriend.
What? Yes, that's right.
It's not like a red valley at all. If I say "red valley," it's kind of a sad story.
It sounds sad, but if you're taking care of someone you're not involved with...
What? But if it's between the parties involved, isn't it possible?
Eh?
No?
No, I don't think it's right to say that.
What?
I can't do it either.
You're saying it, aren't you? I'm not saying it. I'm not saying it.
That's funny.
You got the information from Cocoon, didn't you? No, no, no, no.
False information.
Nowadays, you see, we live in a social networking society.
I've heard it all around me.
Fake news.
Okay, well, maybe what I said was close to that, but it's okay.
I said it at Christmas, and now I think about it, and it's pretty fucking embarrassing.
It's embarrassing.
I'd love to hear a line from someone who's said something stylish and embarrassing.
Like, "I said this at Christmas.
Let's recruit a few.
A cold story.
What are you talking about?
Come on, come on. Only Servon would say such a cold thing.
It's like I'm the one saying it.
It's a social networking society...
I'm afraid of social networking.
Is that what social networking is?
That's the way it is.
It can't be helped.
It's best not to be like you.
Hmm?
It's best not to be on social media like you.
Don't be silly, I do it all the time.
I'm on it.
I'm all over social networking sites.
I'm wearing a T-shirt that says "social networking" on it.
That's weird.
Social networking services?
That's stupid.
That's how addicted I am to it.
That's right.
I'm addicted.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Well, then, let's see...
Let's start with a letter.
Let's see...
This is interesting...
I heard there's a store.
A store?
Oh, the dancing Nippori Ebibuddy.
Yes?
It's a little too sad.
I got a comment about how he said he didn't like to see the illumination when I asked him to go.
I asked a girl to go see the illumination.
She said she didn't like the illumination so much.
Isn't that sad?
I'm pretty sure that's just an excuse to say no.
Please don't go to the illumination.
What's with this commentator?
I don't know... if you put it that way, it might be true.
This MC is too free.
Why don't you use a little more subtlety?
He's too straightforward.
I didn't get the pico-pico hammer.
Why did you bring it?
Why do I have to do it first?
I was trying to be a little milder with this.
Why do you have to do it to me?
It's the other way around.
There's a punchline here, too, right?
That's right.
Dancing Nipporini Livibuddy
Arakawa Ward, Tokyo
Christmas is all about the cake!
It seems he is that cake shop!
I heard that the cake shop was originally a cake shop, and still is!
But the owner of the cake shop loves ramen so much that he wants to open a ramen shop as well.
He really wanted to open a ramen shop too.
So he opened a ramen shop on the opposite side of his cake shop.
The cake shop is his main business, so he can't do it every day.
but he also runs a ramen shop on the other side of his cake shop.
I heard there is a super store that also runs a ramen shop.
So he sent me a picture of it.
Thank you very much!
But it's amazing that you can go eat cake for dessert!
I see. After this...
It's so good! I see.
It's not impossible.
By the way... the store...
The cake shop looks like this.
The cake shop is adorable.
I wonder if it's like this during Halloween.
Like this. This is the cake shop.
And...
The other side of this cake shop
It's just like a back entrance to this store.
This is actually the entrance to a ramen shop.
Well, it's kind of a know-it-all
I know, I'm a little nervous
Go ahead and try it.
Go ahead.
And then...
Tsukemen noodles like this.
Looks delicious.
They seem to love it there.
So they're making that kind of tsukemen?
Because they deal with wheat for cakes and such, they must get good wheat.
I see.
You have a good eye.
I hadn't thought of that.
I don't really understand you anymore, since you're this commentator.
When he does it, he does it.
He's full of crap.
That's right.
That's what he says.
I give out information, but...
But if you're listening to me, you're like... when does he do that?
That's right.
How should I put it?
"Which is it today?
That's what TV is all about.
Don't be like that.
A 17-year-old is talking about TV.
That's not what I'm saying.
That's how it is.
I haven't done it for decades.
That's the way it is.
Well, well, well.
It's just like a dog, isn't it? Yes, it is.
I like the idea of doing both.
That's right. You know, in our heads, we think...
But in reality, it's often impossible.
Yes, that's right. But if you really try, you might be surprised how well it works out.
I'm really impressed by this cake shop owner's energy.
Merry Christmas! Cool!
Merry Christmas to your energy! Oh, cool!
What are you doing? What's with the dancing?
That noodle is sparkling, sparkling, sparkling. It's like he's looking forward to it.
Well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well, well...
Well, then...
I'll tell you something else...
Cannai Debut Festivle!
Well, of course, it's the 23rd of February, right?
On Sunday the 3rd, we'll be holding the Cannai Deb Festivle, and I'd like to show you some of the goods we'll be selling, along with everyone else.
I'd like to show you some of our goods, and I'd like to show you our national transportation version, which I showed you last week.
We also have a national transportation version.
etted
I see that you have the same pose as the poster of the cartoon version.
I see... now I can tell who's who.
I see... I see...
I'm the only one who didn't.
I didn't pose like this.
Wrong concept!
What's that? Error.
Error.
But it looks like it, doesn't it?
It's kind of close.
But it's not the same.
The angle of the tone is the same.
Well, this is an acrylic stand.
Here's the acrylic stand.
I've got one for each of you.
I'm going to climb a mountain too.
There's a mountain there...
Tell me...
It's kinda cool.
It's like we're really climbing a mountain.
Wow!
That's cool.
Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes, yes...
Oh, here it comes... Festivo!
Festivo!
And...
And... over there...
Over there...
Let's start with this one.
I've already introduced you to ours.
Thank you very much.
We have a burial mound version.
Like this.
Look at them all!
It's a special one, but they're all like this.
They're all attached like this
Yuno's hand height
You're right, how many millimeters does it say? It says how many millimeters in diameter, right?
10 or 20 millimeters?
By getting this.
By getting this, it's the same as the back of your hand. I see.
Isn't he a genius? A pseudo handshake?
It might have that effect, but in our case they don't match.
A little more... yes... almost... almost...
75 mm, 7.5 cm.
I'll be back to climb the mountain again.
I'll send it up the mountain.
Can I have it on this side?
Yes, yes.
Like an offering.
It looks like an offering.
And here's a shiny wristband.
Cool.
Let's have him turn it off once and turn it on again.
I'll ask him to turn it on.
It's off.
And...
It's a little darker now.
It's like dusk.
I'll turn it on.
One or the other.
I'm about to turn it on.
Then go darker.
It's getting darker and darker.
It's getting darker.
Under the circumstances...
Go ahead.
Wow!
It's glowing!
Like this.
This is so light. It's just this part.
It's so light.
I can wear many of them.
Only for people who want their whole arm to glow.
Like this.
You can put a whole bunch of them here.
And they're
It's a size that fits so many people.
I see.
It's made relatively large.
Yes, yes, yes.
And, as I introduced last week
Er, towels.
Yes, towels. I don't think there is a house without a towel, but this is a towel from Kannon TV.
I think it would be a nice souvenir to give to the people in your house. And then there is that other thing...
What do you call that clear card with the famous rare scene? Clear card?
Trading card
This one is signed by Mr. Cocoon, isn't it?
Yes, sir.
I heard there's one with his autograph on it.
We also wrote our own autographs on them.
We've included it.
If you see something like that, you might be surprised...
It's possible that it might happen.
But it's very rare.
The old-fashioned monitor that we call a monitor...
It's true.
Cocoon, you're a little young.
This is the most terrifying thing I've ever seen.
Wow, he's growing up.
If I win with Axter, I get to enjoy the growth.
It's amazing.
He's changed so much in a year or two.
I've been here four years now.
He's an adult.
Shaw's an adult, right?
That's why...
And also...
I showed you the bowl of 9-ton coupons last time, so...
Yes, today I'm actually going to recommend...
You know...
There is an instant ramen from Kyushu, called Ronryu, which is sold in some supermarkets, but you can't find it unless you go to a company that puts a lot of effort into it.
Oh!
It's hard to believe that it's instant.
So much!
I bought it this time.
I wondered what would happen if I put ramen in it.
It's so good!
It makes you hungry, doesn't it?
So, the ramen is not ready yet.
I'm still waiting...
I wonder if I should do that, or have a cup of coffee?
If so...
Or...
But...
I'm almost done. Oh, well, let's wait a bit.
In the meantime, I'll get you that Christmas loneliness.
That's right, the Christmas I missed you series.
I like the "I missed you" series. The "I missed you" series.
The "I missed you" series.
I missed you series. I'm sure there are a lot of them.
There will be.
I don't know, maybe it'll be a lonely show, but maybe hearing something like that will make you want to hang in there.
I don't want to be that person.
Don't be alone in this. We want to be a part of it, too.
We can do our best. There are people out there who are doing their best.
I don't want to be like that.
Don't be quiet.
Great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great, great.
That's great, that's great, that's great, that's great.
Uh, but I'm getting a lot of comments, so I'm kind of missing the old ones, but now they're gone, so you just sent me this one, which is why I'm a little sad about Christmas, because I'm collecting them.
If you're sad, it's not because I'm collecting them, it's because I'm happy to change the subject, it's because I finally got a picohane of a comment.
No, no, no, I know exactly what I'm talking about.
That's the sound!
This is how ramen noodles are!
Here comes the ramen!
Oh, here they come!
Don't make a bumping sound, it's coming from behind!
From behind!
He attacked from behind, you coward!
You're such a coward!
Wow!
The shame of being a samurai.
This is so authentic!
It's so good!
Not bad at all.
Looks delicious.
Does it come with this?
No, no, no, no.
I had this prepared separately.
It's like this. When you actually put the ramen in...
Shall we be quiet for a moment? What kind of dance is that?
What kind of dance is that?
And here, let me show you what it looks like when it's in the bowl.
I just showed it to you all.
I'll share it with you. I'll share with you two...
Ron Ryu's Ron Ryu...
Wait a minute. The most exciting moment in the recording process is this one.
Yes, of course. I understand. It's not so exciting here.
Okay, okay, okay.
This is for one person. I'm sorry, it's a little small.
It's totally fine.
The noodles are good.
It's hard to believe they're from Shokuseki.
I put meat in it for the young ones.
I'm sure there's enough meat for the master.
No, no, no...
Eggs are a must, right?
That's right.
Eggs, too.
I'll put them in.
And, oh, the yolk fell out.
Yes, and...
Then soup.
That's it.
The ramen bowl is black. It makes the ramen look good.
That's right.
There's a huge line for this ramen.
That's right. The red font is nice, too.
The red letters...
I thought the expression was a little bad myself. It's a little strange to have a restaurant in the red.
Maybe I'm not acting well. There's been a lot of illumination incidents.
Did anything happen? He asked me to go see it.
I told him it was too cold, so we went inside where it was warm.
I see... that's what I was thinking.
A 17-year-old says...
I prepared presents and they were stolen... by a complete stranger?
Is that possible?
Thank you very much.
We also have green onions... and a convenience show.
What an amazing restaurant!
I'll have a bowl of this.
I'll take the top!
I don't care how many onions I eat.
It smells great!
Merry Christmas!
It's so good!
It's delicious!
It's so much better than those instant noodles.
The noodles are so realistic!
It's so real!
Real.
I know what you mean.
Oh, my God!
Meat
Yum!
Umami!
I love it... it really looks like you're eating at a ramen shop!
Bowl of rice on top of a bowl
Nice Christmas!
I think I'll have tonkotsu ramen for Christmas.
I've never heard of that before.
It's true.
Ryu is the dragon of dragons.
That's cool.
I hope you guys like it.
I think they're doing it for sure.
You can order from one serving. Or rather, you can order from one bag.
The bag is for one person. Usually it's for two or three.
It's for one person or something.
You can eat it whenever you want.
If you keep this at home, you can have it anytime.
We have great ramen, so come over.
For Christmas? I see.
But it's not a good idea to start off by inviting someone over.
That's great. That's deep. Scary, isn't it?
I don't think it's a good idea to ask someone to come over because you have ramen noodles.
Great! Yum!
Where did you get this pork?
Isn't it delicious?
The pork is really good.
Very authentic!
It's very thick.
Yes, it was.
What kind of show is it?
It's not a music show.
The ajitama is delicious!
Ajitama is delicious.
Delicious!
Master, perhaps?
Always.
Like this?
Soup.
I got ramen soup on my nose.
Mr. mustache...
Good night.
We've received a debut charge from Cocoon to cover the cost of our Christmas party.
Thank you very much!
This is the first year I'm buying delicious cookies for everyone!
That's nice.
You don't sound like a normal girl.
I'm a pretty good cook.
That's for sure.
You can make sweets too?
Amazing.
She's got a lot of potential.
Yes, it is.
It's called "Potato Chips".
Potato chips.
Last year...
I gave everyone muffins for Valentine's Day.
Yushi from Jadal wished us good luck at the Christmas concert.
He's giving them to me.
He's so cool!
I'll leave it to him!
Today's jacket is cool too!
By the way, you'll see for the first time when you finish the soup.
This is the world of the abyss!
Message
I like it.
I like the way the oil is shining.
It's very graphic.
Yes, sir.
That's why I said yes.
It was delicious.
Delicious.
Thank you for the food
I really feel refreshed after eating ramen
I drank all the soup!
What the hell?
Amazing!
Delicious!
Thank you so much for the food!
Well, well, well...
Well then...
Well, now that we're accepting orders for all kinds of goods, we'd like to invite you all to buy them at home, too.
Yes, acryl mustard. Please let me climb a mountain near your house.
On the mountain near your house, Master.
It's really cool... this picture... it's like they're the ones who made it.
So, I guess it's time to talk... about that important announcement...
Ticket sales for the Saitama Super Arena concert on March 20, 2025 will end at 23:59 today.
I know there were a lot of people who were planning to buy the tickets later last time, so I don't think that will happen, but I really want you to buy the tickets.
I really hope you'll buy it.
We have no choice but to work hard from here, so all the members will do our best so that everyone will follow us.
If you're interested, I'd be happy if you came!
So, if you're interested, I'd love it if you'd come to the show.
I'll tell you what, today is November 20...
Today is November 20/7.
November's early.
It's only November 30.
12, 12, 3...
And February is only 28.
That's not much.
Well, well, well.
I'm looking forward to it, though.
I think it's my duty as an idol to entertain everyone at the concert.
I think it's my duty as an idol, so I'm going to do my best to make sure that I can entertain everyone.
I'll definitely do my best to entertain you.
No, no, no, no, no, no... when you decided to do this...
No, no, no, no, no...
We'll be there on the day of the show, of course, but it's quite a distance from Yokohama, you know...
It's a long way from Yokohama, so we always say we won't be able to catch the last train after the show.
We're talking about staying at a business hotel in Omiya or something.
I'll see you all again next week at 8:00 p.m.
Thank you very much for your time this week.
Thank you very much.